<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Environment Setup on SAP on Microsoft - Tutorials</title>
    <link>https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/env_setup/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Environment Setup on SAP on Microsoft - Tutorials</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 16:31:36 -0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/env_setup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Azure Setup for SAP CAL</title>
      <link>https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/env_setup/azure_setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 16:34:27 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/env_setup/azure_setup/</guid>
      <description>SAP has a platform called SAP Cloud Application Library (SAP CAL), designed to automatically deploys SAP software on cloud hyperscalers.
In order to allow for SAP to deploy an S/4HANA environment in your Azure subscription, we need to setup permissions for it in your subscription.
This section will go thru the steps required to setup your subscription
What you will need  An existing Azure subscription with enough credits for the labs Administrator access on the subscription A temporary text file to make note of the required information related to endpoints and keys   Warning In order to be able to deploy on your subscription, permissions used here will be quite broad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAP Cloud Appliance Library (CAL)</title>
      <link>https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/env_setup/sap_cal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 17:27:06 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/env_setup/sap_cal/</guid>
      <description>The SAP Cloud Appliance Library (CAL) offers a quick and easy way to consume the latest SAP solutions in the cloud, such as SAP S/4HANA, SAP HANA Express Edition, Industry Solutions etc.
It&amp;rsquo;s an online library of latest, preconfigured, ready-to-use SAP solutions that can be instantly deployed into your own public cloud accounts.
In this section we will create and account on SAP CAL, configure Azure permissions and deploy an S/4HANA environment on your subscription.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft On-premises Data Gateway Installation</title>
      <link>https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/env_setup/datagwsetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 11:21:23 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/env_setup/datagwsetup/</guid>
      <description>Once SAP is installed and access is working, we need to install the required components to allow for Microsoft services to interact with SAP S/4HANA environments.
The on-premises data gateway acts as a bridge to provide quick and secure data transfer between on-premises data (data that isn&amp;rsquo;t in the cloud) and several Microsoft cloud services. These cloud services include Power BI, PowerApps, Power Automate, Azure Analysis Services, and Azure Logic Apps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAP Gateway Demo System</title>
      <link>https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/env_setup/demogw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 09:17:38 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/env_setup/demogw/</guid>
      <description>Some demos will demand mock data and ODATA APIs to demosntrate SAP integration. Once the purpose of this demos are to show the integration itself, and not how to build those APIs, we will leverage an ready to be used SAP Gateway Demo System with everything we need.
This is a free service for which we need to create and account and define credentials for access. In this sectiopn we will go thru the steps required for you to have an account and credentials for it.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>