<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Sentinel on SAP on Microsoft - Tutorials</title>
    <link>https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/labs/security/sentinel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Microsoft Sentinel on SAP on Microsoft - Tutorials</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 14:22:13 -0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/labs/security/sentinel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Create Sentinel</title>
      <link>https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/labs/security/sentinel/step1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 14:22:13 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/labs/security/sentinel/step1/</guid>
      <description>Before we start integrating SAP with Microsoft Sentinel, we need to setup components to allow this communication to happen.
This section will show the steps required for this to be accomplished:
Setting up Log Analytics Go to Azure Portal, click on Create Resource and look for Log Analytics Workspaces Click Create Fill in the required informations: Subscription: SELECT YOUR SUBSCRIPTION Resource Group: SAP CAL Resource Group Name: SAPLogAnalyticsWorkspace Region: East US Click on Review + create and then Create Creating a Microsoft Sentinel workspace Go to Azure Portal, click on Create Resource and look for Microsoft Sentinel Click Create Select the previously created SAPLogAnalyticsWorkspace and click Add If this is your first Microsoft Sentinel, accept the Trial On the Get Started click on go to Content Hub so we can add SAP log model to Sentinel Look for SAP, select the Solution and click Install On the next screen, click Create Fill in the required informations: Subscription: SELECT YOUR SUBSCRIPTION Resource Group: SAP CAL Resource Group Deployment Target Workspace: SAPLogAnalyticsWorkspace Click on Review + create and then Create Alright!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Setup SAP</title>
      <link>https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/labs/security/sentinel/step2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 14:22:13 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/labs/security/sentinel/step2/</guid>
      <description>Now we will prepare and configure SAP to send the logs to Sentinel Agent, which will be deployed later on.
Downloading SAP Change Requests Log on to the SAP S/4HANA host via SSH (or Putty) ssh -i SAPCALKey.pem root@S4HANAIP On the host console, create a directory and download the Change Requests: cd mkdir CRs cd CRs wget -q https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Azure/Azure-Sentinel/master/Solutions/SAP/CR/K900271.NPL wget -q https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Azure/Azure-Sentinel/master/Solutions/SAP/CR/R900271.NPL wget -q https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Azure/Azure-Sentinel/master/Solutions/SAP/CR/K900202.NPL wget -q https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Azure/Azure-Sentinel/master/Solutions/SAP/CR/R900202.NPL wget -q https://raw.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy Sentinel SAP Agent</title>
      <link>https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/labs/security/sentinel/step3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 14:22:13 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/labs/security/sentinel/step3/</guid>
      <description>Now that the configuration steps are done, we are ready to deploy the agent that will gather SAP logs and dispatch them to Azure Sentinel.
Warning SAP SOFTWARE DOWNLOAD
In order to be able to deploy the agent, we will need to download SAP Netweaver SDK directly from SAP Downloads. Although it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a cost, it will require an SAP user with software download permissions.
Please before continuing make sure you have an SAP user with proper permissions to download the required software or you won&amp;rsquo;t be able to continue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting 1st vulnerability</title>
      <link>https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/labs/security/sentinel/step4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 14:22:13 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/labs/security/sentinel/step4/</guid>
      <description>We have the logs being pushed to Sentinel. Let&amp;rsquo;s configure the data connectors to handle SAP logs on Azure Sentinel.
In this first example we will monitor for a security vulnerability regarding user creation, where an users create a new user using SAP transaction SU01 and then log in using the newly created user from the same IP. This might be a Discovery technique used by attackers.
Creating our rule During the first part of this tutorial, we created a Log Analytics, connected it with Sentinel and installed the connector for SAP logs.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>