<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Automation and Integration on SAP on Microsoft - Tutorials</title>
    <link>https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/labs/autoint/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Automation and Integration on SAP on Microsoft - Tutorials</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 11:55:21 -0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/labs/autoint/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Azure Logic Apps</title>
      <link>https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/labs/autoint/logicapps/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 11:58:35 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/labs/autoint/logicapps/</guid>
      <description>Azure Logic Apps Azure Logic Apps is a cloud-based platform for creating and running automated workflows that integrate your apps, data, services, and systems. With this platform, you can quickly develop highly scalable integration solutions for your enterprise and business-to-business (B2B) scenarios. As a member of Azure Integration Services, Azure Logic Apps simplifies the way that you connect legacy, modern, and cutting-edge systems across cloud, on premises, and hybrid environments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power Virtual Agent</title>
      <link>https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/labs/autoint/virtualagents/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 11:58:35 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/labs/autoint/virtualagents/</guid>
      <description>Power Virtual Agent Microsoft Power Virtual Agents lets you create powerful chatbots that can answer questions posed by your customers, other employees, or visitors to your website or service.
These bots can be created easily without the need for data scientists or developers. Some of the ways that Power Virtual Agents bots have been used include:
 Sales help and support issues Product or Purchase Order informations Employee health and vacation benefits Common employee questions for businesses, products, processes  All this integrated with live SAP data, allowing customers to access the information they need, on a simple, common, practical platform they are used to, avoiding the burden of context switching between multiples apps to accomplish a task.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power Apps</title>
      <link>https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/labs/autoint/powerapps/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 11:58:35 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/labs/autoint/powerapps/</guid>
      <description>Power Apps Power Apps is a suite of apps, services, and connectors, as well as a data platform, that provides a rapid development environment to build custom apps for your business needs. Using Power Apps, you can quickly build custom business apps that connect to your data stored either in the underlying data platform (Microsoft Dataverse) or in various online and on-premises data sources (such as SAP, SharePoint, Microsoft 365, Dynamics 365, SQL Server, and so on).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power Automate Flow</title>
      <link>https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/labs/autoint/office365flow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 11:58:35 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/labs/autoint/office365flow/</guid>
      <description>Power Automate Power Automate is a service that helps you create automated workflows between your favorite apps and services to synchronize files, get notifications, collect data, and more.
Here are a few examples of what you can do with Power Automate.
 Automate business processes Send automatic reminders for past due tasks Move business data between systems on a schedule Connect to more than 500 data sources or any publicly available API You can even automate tasks on your local computer like computing data in Excel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power Automate RPA</title>
      <link>https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/labs/autoint/automate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 11:58:35 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/labs/autoint/automate/</guid>
      <description>COMING SOON Please check back in a few days …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power BI</title>
      <link>https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/labs/autoint/powerbi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/labs/autoint/powerbi/</guid>
      <description>COMING SOON Please check back in a few days &amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Builder</title>
      <link>https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/labs/autoint/aibuilder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://abicas.github.io/SapOnMicrosoftDemos/labs/autoint/aibuilder/</guid>
      <description>COMING SOON Please check back in a few days &amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>